<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<lang xmlns="http://wedge.org/xml/importer/lang" xmlns:smf="http://wedge.org" languagecode="en">
	<item name="we.imp.locale">en</item>
	<item name="we.imp.which_software"><![CDATA[Which software are you using?]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.multiple_files"><![CDATA[The importer found multiple import data files. Please choose the one you wish to use.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_here"><![CDATA[It's not here!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.check_more"><![CDATA[If the software you're looking for doesn't appear above, please check to see if it is available for download at <a href="http://wedge.org/">wedge.org</a>. If it isn't, we may be able to write one for you - just ask us!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.having_problems"><![CDATA[If you're having any other problems with this importer, don't hesitate to look for help on our <a href="http://wedge.org">forum</a>.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_found"><![CDATA[The importer did not find any import data files. Please check to see if the one you want is available for download at <a href="http://wedge.org/">wedge.org</a>. If it isn't, we may be able to write one for you - just ask us!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_found_download"><![CDATA[After you download it, simply upload it into the same folder as <b>this import.php file</b>. If you're having any other problems with this importer, don't hesitate to look for help on our <a href="http://wedge.org">forum</a>.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.try_again"><![CDATA[Try again!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.settings_not_found"><![CDATA[This importer was unable to find Wedge in the path you specified. Please double check the path, and that it is already installed there.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.open_basedir"><![CDATA[The importer detected that your host has open_basedir enabled on this server. Please ask your host to disable this setting or try moving the contents of your %s to the public html folder of your site.']]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.config_not_found"><![CDATA[Unable to find the settings for %s. Please double check the path and try again.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.password_incorrect"><![CDATA[The database password you entered was incorrect. Please make sure you are using the right password (for the Wedge user!) and try it again. If in doubt, use the password from Settings.php in the Wedge installation.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.select_step"><![CDATA[You must select at least one step to import.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.permission_denied"><![CDATA[Sorry, the database connection information used in the specified installation of Wedge cannot access the installation of %1. This may either mean that the installation doesn't exist, or that the MySQL account used does not have permissions to access it.<br /><br />The error MySQL gave was: ']]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.before_continue"><![CDATA[Before you continue]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.before_details"><![CDATA[This importer assumes you have already installed Wedge and that your installation is working properly. It copies members, posts and other data from your &quot;source&quot; installation of %s into Wedge, so it won't work without an installation of Wedge.<p>All or some of the data in your installation of Wedge will be <b>overwritten</b>.</p>]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.wedge_installed"><![CDATA[Try again!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.where"><![CDATA[Where are they?]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.locate_wedge"><![CDATA[The importer should only need to know where the two installations are, after which it should be able to handle everything for itself.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.advanced_options"><![CDATA[Advanced options]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.path_to_wedge"><![CDATA[Path to Wedge]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.path_to_source"><![CDATA[Path to]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.restart_after"><![CDATA[pause script after (seconds)]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.countdown"><![CDATA[Javascript countdown (sleep)]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.right_path"><![CDATA[This may be the right path.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.change_path"><![CDATA[You will need to change the value in this box.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.database_passwd"><![CDATA[Wedge database password]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.database_verify"><![CDATA[The MySQL password (for verification only.)]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.selected_only"><![CDATA[Import selected areas only]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.empty_log"><![CDATA[Empty the import error log?]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.continue"><![CDATA[Continue]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_this"><![CDATA[Not this software?]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.skipped"><![CDATA[skipped]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_found_skipped"><![CDATA[not found, skipped]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.pick_different"><![CDATA[If this is the wrong software, you can go back and <a href="%s?import_script=">pick a different data file</a>.)]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.recalculate"><![CDATA[Recalculating forum statistics]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.importing"><![CDATA[Importing]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.complete"><![CDATA[Import complete!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.congrats"><![CDATA[Congratulations, the importer has completed successfully. If you have or had any problems with this importer, or need help using Wedge, please feel free to <a href="http://wedge.org">look to us for support</a>.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.check_box"><![CDATA[Please check this box to delete the importer right now for security reasons.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.may_fail"><![CDATA[doesn't work on all servers.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.not_done"><![CDATA[Not quite done yet!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.importer_paused"><![CDATA[The importer has paused a few seconds to avoid overloading your server. Don't worry though, <b>nothing's wrong</b>.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.all_imported"><![CDATA[Now that everything is imported, your Wedge installation should have all the data from the %s installation.]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.smooth_transition"><![CDATA[We hope you had a smooth transition!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.invalid"><![CDATA[Installation invalid, please double-check your path!]]></item>
	<item name="we.imp.validated"><![CDATA[Installation validated!]]></item>
</lang>